The SCOAN Sunday Service
It's alright.
During a Sunday service, there is a seeming distraction in the congregation.
We can see here, a young man creating a scene.
Brother!
Please take it easy.
Come. What's wrong? Come.
I want to get married, I am not yet married.
You want to get married?
Yes, sir.
And you are not yet married?
What a handsome man! Come.
He says, he wants to get married and he is not yet married - very handsome man. Don't worry.
Take one.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Go and wait for me. Okay? You will come back and give testimony here.
Somebody says he wants to get married and you are blocking him.
TESTIMONY CONTINUES
Hallelujah. Let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ!
Testimony Time
Emmanuel! (God With Us - Matthew 1:23)
Good Morning!
My name is Deacon Prince Uche Anazodo, and this is my wife. My beautiful Pina pina.
Her name is Princess Kenechi Vivian Anazodo. Praise the Lord!
You have already seen the clips. It was a terrible situation.
Before I came to the SCOAN, I had this challenge of not being able to get married.
It was not ordinary. It was a challenge. It was a demonic conception.
I am a deacon, I had a challenge, inspite of my church commitment and what have you.
The time I intended to get married, I discovered that I couldn't get married.
It's either, I like the woman, she doesn't like me; or she likes me and I would not be able to like her.
And even if she likes me and I like her, it will not work.
And a scenario, the lady in question died. It was so terrible! In fact, as a matter of fact,
it came to a point, my father - though he is late now - took it as a point of duty
to make me get married. In fact, he took me to a lady. At a point he said "My son, you have to get married."
It was like an embarrassment. And you know, at a point I was downcased.
I had a lot of thoughts in me - suicidal and what have you.
But I remembered, there was a man, a man of God in the person of Prophet T.B. Joshua, the Senior Prophet.
Prince Uche and Princess Kenechi Anazodo - Prophesy Testimony
I took a decision to go to the pilgrimage. You know, here is a pilgrimage, here it's not just a church setting.
To have an encounter with the Man of God.
And when I came - the church was actually winding up, and the Man of God in the Synagogue
was not looking at my direction. I said: "Wow". I said: "No, I can't go here empty handed."
I said: "God, You have to help me because I know what it takes
to see the Man of God without him inviting you."
So I prayed a simple prayer. I said: "Lord, have Your way."
And from what you saw in the clips; I stood up, the ushers came running around me,
but God had to intervene because my case was desperate.
My case was different. Emmanuel!
So, when he beckoned on me, and he asked me: "Young man, what's the problem?"
I told him: "I want to get married. But I discovered that it was not ordinary. My own case is not an ordinary case."
He now said, very simple. He said I will come back and give my testimony.
I said: "So simple!" So when I went back, God is a good Arrenger.
So He had to arrange me. And gave me the favour.
Actually, I am an engineer, I install, supply dishes and what have you, CCTV camera and what have you.
So I got an arrangement and I started working in the palace,
of the King of my town. So when I started working there it now happened that... It was on a certain day,
one wonderful day.
Her Majesty called me, she said they have a challenge. I should come and know what is happening,
what was the problem. So I went there, and before you could say...
I saw my wife now passing by. I said: "Who is this person?"
They said, it is the daughter of the King, the daughter of Igwe. I said: "Ah!"
Prince Uche & Princess Kenechi Anazodo - Prophecy Testimony
So, I now went to her, I approached her. I introduced myself.
And she now introduced herself. She just graduated, she came back trying to prepare
for her Youth Service. So we now started talking and we exchanged our phone numbers.
She said that since I'm into installation of satellite dishes and what have you,
when she gets where she is posted, she would want me to come and install a satellite dish for her.
That was how it begun, and before we knew it, it now came from installing of satellite dish
to installation for marriage.
And before you know it, it was an installation of pregnancy.
The God of Senior Prophet T.B. Joshua is the authentic, autocratic, authoritative, automatical.
God of Prophet T.B. Joshua is the God, that is beyond human comprehension.
The impossibility Specialist.
The God that knows the ending from the beginning.
I want to give Him all the Glory! He is worthy. Hallelujah!
Amen. Let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ.
And brother, we want to ask you; when you came to the SCOAN and had this encounter
with Prophet T.B. Joshua, when you returned home, what was the reaction of people who saw you
on Emmanuel TV crying out? What did they tell you when you went home?
Actually when I went home, they were laughing at me. My friends, they were saying
I went to the Synagogue to eat apple. Where is the woman?
It was not an easy, it was not an easy encounter. I was like: "Wow".
But today this is my woman. You can see her live and direct. Hallelujah!
Amen! Lets put our hands together for Jesus Christ.
And brother, we can see some pictures on the board there. Could you describe to us what we are seeing here.
This is my court wedding certificate.
This is my white wedding certificate.
This is my court wedding. You can see me here. This is my pina pina, my wife.
This is the court wedding.
This is the church wedding. You can see me here. This is my pina pina, my princess.
This is the church event.
Let me introduce my father in law to you. This is Igwe Doctor K.O.N. Orizu.
The Igwe Nnewi and this is the daughter.
This is the Igwe Orizo III,
Igwe Doctor K.N.O Orizo III. Igwe Nnewi Traditional ruler of Nnewi Kingdom.
Ordinarily there was no way I could have gotten married to the daughter of Igwe,
if not of God's intervention through the Prophet himself, Prophet T.B. Joshua.
Amen! Lets put our hands together for Jesus Christ.
This is the traditional wedding. In fact, I am overwhelmed. I am overgusted, I am overwhelmed.
Glory to God Almighty.
And since you got married you have enjoyed peace and love in this marriage and the curse that didn't want
you to get married has truly been broken.
Actually, my wife here, my wonderful, beautiful, joyful princess,
since I got married to her, I have been enjoying peace. Very humble, as you see her,
she is very humble to the core. Very down to earth.
You know, just like my father in the Lord Prophet T.B. Joshua, humble.
So I want to give God the Glory. She is wonderful woman, very peaceful.
She doesn't want trouble, she doesn't like trouble.
And the family is a wonderful family. It is wonderful family. It was through divine arrangement;
because everything was divinely arranged.
You can't imagine me getting married to the daughter of Igwe. It's not possible.
It's not. Naturally, there is no way. "Who dash Monkey Banana."
Indeed, this is divine arrangement, and we give all the Glory to God Almighty,
for what He has done in the life of our brother here.
And do you mean to say, sir, that in your family you have been facing this problem of not being able to get married?
This has been a curse in the family but that curse has been broken, through your coming here?
Yes, it was actually a curse. I am the only son. You know what that means.
If you have an only son, and your only son is not able to get married - you know what that means.
That means the lineage is going. And when I knew it,
I knew it was not a church thing. You have to go to seek the face of the field marshal.
You need to seek the face of the faith marshal. We have generals actually,
but we have a field martial. And I had to go and seek the face of the field marshal
in the person of senior Prophet T.B. Joshua.
Amen! And today we can see the results in the life of our brother.
Right now we want hear a quick word from your wife as well before coming back to hear you advice.
Emmanuel! My name is Princess Kenechi Vivian Anazodo.
When we were about to get married, it was a surprise to everybody.
People were like: "Are you sure this daughter of Igwe and all that?" In fact, they said many things,
But thank God. One thing I know that with God everything is possible.
Glory be to God, and today you are happily married to your husband.
And you have listened to this wonderful testimony. What can you say about what God has done?
God is a marvelous God. He is indeed wonderful. Thank you, Jesus.
Finally, brother, we would like to hear your word of advice to our viewers all over the world
in the light of this wonderful testimony.
Praise the Lord. I would like to use this opportunity to advice my Christian brothers.
Praise the Lord. It's good to be in a denomination but when you now discover that your case
has now become a chronic case, please my brothers, my sisters - run down to the SCOAN.
Run down to the SCOAN to have an encounter. This is not a church thing.
God is not interested in you being a church member. Praise the Lord!
God is interested in you having an encounter with destiny and this is the place of destiny.
Praise the Lord! This is pilgrimage ground. People go to Israel for pilgrimage.
Please run down here, this is pilgrimage ground. When you come here, you have an encounter with your destiny.
If you are not able to get married, just as I was, you are going to come back
with your wife to share the testimony in this place, in the name of Jesus.
Amen. Lets put our hands for Jesus Christ!
Thank you, Jesus Christ! And we heard it all from our brother. We know that our membership
at our local church is merely symbolic. What counts is Christ in us, the Hope of Glory.
And we believe that as Christians we are all one in the body of Christ.
On the last day when we stand before Jesus, the question will not be:
"Did you worship in this church or worship in this denomination?"
But the question will be: "Did you worship in Spirit and in Truth?"
And we thank God for what he has done in the life of this couple and we believe more and more
testimonies are on the way. As Prophet T.B Joshua says - better is not good enough
the best is yet to come, in Jesus' name. Lets put our hands together for Jesus Christ one more time!
TT Monica Asefa 27/07/18
RV: Pavel Tatyana Zheleznyakov 09/08/2018